d = {
   "questions":[
      {
         "answer":"Gullible",
         "options":[
            "Malleable",
            "Futile",
            "Distill"
         ],
         "question":"Easily deceived"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Placate",
         "options":[
            "Platitude",
            "Piety",
            "Satiate"
         ],
         "question":"Pacify; Conciliate"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Plasticity",
         "options":[
            "Alacrity",
            "Paucity",
            "Compliant"
         ],
         "question":"Ability to be molded"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Inconsequential",
         "options":[
            "Recondite",
            "Indeterminate",
            "Tangential"
         ],
         "question":"Insignificant; Unimportant"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Satiate",
         "options":[
            "Saturate",
            "Obviate",
            "Stint"
         ],
         "question":"Satisfy fully"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Loquacious",
         "options":[
            "Audacious",
            "Gullible",
            "Gregarious"
         ],
         "question":"Talkative"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Eclectic",
         "options":[
            "Ascetic",
            "Fallacious",
            "Skeptic"
         ],
         "question":"Selective; Composed of elements drawn from disparate sources"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Impair",
         "options":[
            "Impede",
            "Savor",
            "Shard"
         ],
         "question":"Injure; Hurt"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Fervor",
         "options":[
            "Savor",
            "Negate",
            "Torpor"
         ],
         "question":"Glowing ardor; Intensity of feeling"
      },
      {
         "answer":"Relegate",
         "options":[
            "Negate",
            "Rarefied",
            "Venerate"
         ],
         "question":"Banish to an inferior position; Delegate; Assign"
      }
   ]
}

print(d['questions'][0]['options'][0])